blacklapel.com 2012-06-11

# Black Lapel - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

We are committed to protecting the privacy rights of visitors to [www.BlackLapel.com](http://www.blacklapel.com/).  Black Lapel knows that you care about your personal information and how it is used.  We appreciate your trust.

This policy covers how Black Lapel Custom Clothiers, Inc. (“Black Lapel”) treats personal information that Black Lapel collects and receives.  This includes information related to past transactions with Black Lapel. 

Under the terms of this policy, personal information refers to information about you that is personally identifiable and not otherwise publicly available.  This may include, but is not limited to: your name, address, email address or phone number.  This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Black Lapel does not own, control, manage or employ. 

**Collecting Information**

The information we obtain from you helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at our Site. Any personal information you provide to us is maintained on secure servers and our internal systems. It is your choice whether or not to provide personal information. However, any information you provide will be treated with care, and subject to this policy, will not be used or disclosed in ways to which you have not consented.

Black Lapel collects personal information when you register with Black Lapel, when you use Black Lapel products, when you visit Black Lapel pages or the pages of certain Black Lapel partners, and when you enter any promotions or sweepstakes. Black Lapel may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, zip code, occupation, industry, and how you heard about us. Once you register with Black Lapel and sign-in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Once you make a purchase with Black Lapel, Black Lapel will keep your shipping and billing information as well as your measurements and fit preferences for ease of future purchases.  Black Lapel automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Black Lapel cookie information, and the page you request. Black Lapel uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Cookies**

Black Lapel may set and access Black Lapel 'cookies' on your computer. Black Lapel lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Cookies enhance the convenience and use of Black Lapel.com. For example, the information provided through cookies is used to recognize you as a previous user (so you do not have to enter your personal information every time), offer personalized web page content and information for your use, and otherwise facilitate your website experience.  You may decline cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may affect your use of the website.

**Your Information**

You can edit your Black Lapel account information at any time. Black Lapel will automatically send you certain communications relating to the Black Lapel service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Black Lapel Newsletter, that are considered part of your Black Lapel account.  However, if you do not wish to receive e-mail or other mail from Black Lapel, you can unsubscribe at any time. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

As a general policy, Black Lapel does not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other third parties.   The exceptions to this policy are:

(1)   When we provide personal information to trusted partners who work on behalf of, or with, Black Lapel under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Black Lapel communicate with you about offers from Black Lapel and our marketing partners.

(2)   When required by a court or applicable law. 

(3)   To enforce our terms of use. 

(4)   If Black Lapel is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Black Lapel will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

As part of our commitment to protect your personal information, we have physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that are in compliance with federal regulations.

**Policy Updates**

Black Lapel reserves the right to update, alter or modify this policy.  Black Lapel will notify you about changes it reasonably believes are significant under its sole and exclusive judgment.  All such notifications will be sentto the primary email address specified in your Black Lapel account or by placing a prominent notice on our Site.  Following any such changes, continued use of [www.Black Lapel.com](http://www.alphaspoke.com/) constitutes your agreement to be bound by the new terms.
